CHRISTINA THAI

FAMILY NURSE PRACTITIONER

408.655.9523







PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

A Family Nurse Practitioner working in Informatics with 5 years of experience in data analytics and optimizing workflows. Saved my organizations over \$210,000 annually and the staff 160 hours of work a week, while improving clinical outcomes.

EDUCATION

- M.S. in Nursing Family Nurse Practitioner
- · B.S. in Nursing
- B.S. in Biopsychology

Samuel Merritt University, GPA 3.97 Samuel Merritt University, GPA 3.51 University of California, Santa Barbara

CERTIFICATION

- Informatics Nurse, ANCC
- Family Nurse Practitioner, AANP

LICENSURE

• Family Nurse Practitioner, West Virginia Board of Nursing

WORK EXPERIENCE

Data Analyst

Huntington Internal Medical Group | Sep 2022 - present

- Automated the lab charges process, saving the company \$40,000 annually.
- Automated the Medicare Quality Measures process, saving the company \$70,0000 annually & ensuring patients get the preventative care they need.

Research Associate

Marshall Dermatology | Sep 2020 - Sep 2022

• Scanned clinical dermatology photos to be used as teaching aids for medical students & residents.

Clinical Research Analyst

Stanford Health Care - Emergency Department | Jul 2019 - Aug 2020

• Collected and analyzed data for research project on traumatic brain injuries at Stanford ED.

Assistant Nurse Director

Bay Area Laser Cosmetic Surgery Center | Dec 2019 - Mar 2020

• Built a relational database to track the surgery center's progress towards accreditation.

Registered Nurse

Santa Clara Valley Medical Center - Neonatal Intensive Care Unit (NICU) | Apr 2017 - Oct 2018

- Automated the units' workflow & data pipeline, saving the unit \$100,000 annually in addition to improving patient care & data quality.
- Reviewed and revised policies and procedures for delivery room resuscitation (Smart Start).
- Spearheaded the clinical training video series for the new graduate NICU RN program.

WORK EXPERIENCE (CONTINUED)

Optician

For Eyes Optical | Jul 2014 - Jul 2015

• Exceeded weekly sales goal in eyewear and contact lenses, earning our store #1 in district sales 4 months in a row.

Pharmacy Technician

CVS Pharmacy | Jul 2014 - Jul 2015

• Filled over 500 prescriptions a day, making our pharmacy the highest volume CVS pharmacy in the county.

SKILLS

- Python
- 201
- R
- SQL
- Statistical Analysis
- Machine Learning
- · Predictive Modeling
- Tableau
- Power BI
- Access

- Notion
- Web development
- Cerner Code (SMART on FHIR)

PUBLICATIONS SUBMITTED

Reasons for breast milk feeding cessation in infants post NICU discharge

Nudelman M, Patel R, <u>Thai C</u>, Koffman M, Cheng S, Jegatheesan P, Song D, & Govindaswami B. Published in Practice in Neonatal Nursing - Sep 2019

POSTERS

Factors Contributing to Breast Milk Feeding Cessation Post NICU Discharge

Patel R, Nudelman M, Kofman M, Le M, Cheng S, <u>Thai C</u>, Jegatheesan P, Song D, Govindaswami B.

Presented at

- Vermont Oxford Network 2017 (Chicago, Illinois)
- Pediatric Academic Society 2018 (Toronto, Canada)
- The Collaborative Alliance for Nursing Outcomes Conference 2018 (San Diego, California)
- The Collaborative Alliance for Nursing Outcomes Conference Poster Award Winner 2018 (San Diego, California)

VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE

Nurse Health Coach & Recovery Coach

Greater Recovery and Community Empowerment | Sep 2020 - present

• Completed naloxone training, as well as WV Board of Nursing's nurse health coach and recovery coach training.

Nursing Student

HIV Education and Prevention Project of Alameda County (HEPPAC) | Sep 2016

- Provided syringe access and other harm reduction supplies, food, naloxone and other services in West Oakland.
- · Assisted doctor in Mobile Outreach van, providing anonymous and free primary care and HCV/HIV testing.

WORK EXPERIENCE (CONTINUED)

Optician

For Eyes Optical | Jul 2014 - Jul 2015

• Exceeded weekly sales goal in eyewear and contact lenses, earning our store #1 in district sales 4 months in a row.

Pharmacy Technician

CVS Pharmacy | Jul 2014 - Jul 2015

• Filled over 500 prescriptions a day, making our pharmacy the highest volume CVS pharmacy in the county.

PUBLICATIONS SUBMITTED

Reasons for breast milk feeding cessation in infants post NICU discharge

Nudelman M, Patel R, <u>Thai C</u>, Koffman M, Cheng S, Jegatheesan P, Song D, & Govindaswami B. Published in Practice in Neonatal Nursing - Sep 2019

POSTERS

Factors Contributing to Breast Milk Feeding Cessation Post NICU Discharge

Patel R, Nudelman M, Kofman M, Le M, Cheng S, <u>Thai C</u>, Jegatheesan P, Song D, Govindaswami B. Presented at

- Vermont Oxford Network 2017 (Chicago, Illinois)
- Pediatric Academic Society 2018 (Toronto, Canada)
- The Collaborative Alliance for Nursing Outcomes Conference 2018 (San Diego, California) Awards:
 - The Collaborative Alliance for Nursing Outcomes Conference Poster Award Winner 2018 (San Diego, California)

VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE

Nurse Health Coach & Recovery Coach

Greater Recovery and Community Empowerment | Sep 2020 - present

• Completed naloxone training, as well as WV Board of Nursing's nurse health coach and recovery coach training.

Nursing Student

HIV Education and Prevention Project of Alameda County (HEPPAC) | Sep 2016

- Provided syringe access and other harm reduction supplies, food, naloxone and other services in West Oakland.
- Assisted doctor in Mobile Outreach van, providing anonymous and free primary care and HCV/HIV testing.

Family Nurse Practitioner Student

Oakland Youth Football and Cheerleading | Aug 2019

• Provided free sports physicals to entire Oakland Youth Foot'ball and Cheerleading team, children ages 5-12.

Volunteer

Santa Clara Valley Medical Center - 4MED, Gift Shop, Front Desk, and NICU | Jan 2014 - Jul 2017

• Assisted the floor nurses by restocking supplies, as well as answering the units' phone and patients' call bells.